[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "That's what you believe, isn't it, fundamentally?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "believe", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "fundamentally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Yes, give or take a little.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "give", "or", "take", "a", "little", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Why are you not prepared to accept that that means you can move with the times, to evolve it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "not", "prepared", "to", "accept", "that", "that", "means", "you", "can", "move", "with", "the", "times", ",", "to", "evolve", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Oh, I -- but I -- I do accept that, with -- with respect to those vague terms in the Constitution such as equal protection of the laws, due process of law, cruel and unusual punishments.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "--", "but", "I", "--", "I", "do", "accept", "that", ",", "with", "--", "with", "respect", "to", "those", "vague", "terms", "in", "the", "Constitution", "such", "as", "equal", "protection", "of", "the", "laws", ",", "due", "process", "of", "law", ",", "cruel", "and", "unusual", "punishments", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "How do you equate that, as man of fairness and justice, how do you continue to be so pro something which is so obviously flawed?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "equate", "that", ",", "as", "man", "of", "fairness", "and", "justice", ",", "how", "do", "you", "continue", "to", "be", "so", "pro", "something", "which", "is", "so", "obviously", "flawed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I -- I'm not pro.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "pro", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "That -- that becomes a punishment, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "--", "that", "becomes", "a", "punishment", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "No, I don't think it becomes a punishment.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "becomes", "a", "punishment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "But what about if you're an innocent person being waterboarded?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "about", "if", "you", "'re", "an", "innocent", "person", "being", "waterboarded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I'm not for it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "-- isn't it down to the Supreme Court to effectively give a -- a more modern interpretation of the spirit of what that means, to adapt it to modern times?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "n't", "it", "down", "to", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "to", "effectively", "give", "a", "--", "a", "more", "modern", "interpretation", "of", "the", "spirit", "of", "what", "that", "means", ",", "to", "adapt", "it", "to", "modern", "times", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, that's lovely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "lovely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "But why don't you think it is?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, I don't think it is, because, look, the -- the background principle of all of this is democracy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", ",", "because", ",", "look", ",", "the", "--", "the", "background", "principle", "of", "all", "of", "this", "is", "democracy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What did you say in response to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "in", "response", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I said if you're going to be serious about textualism, if the statute does not make an exception, it does not make an exception.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "if", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "serious", "about", "textualism", ",", "if", "the", "statute", "does", "not", "make", "an", "exception", ",", "it", "does", "not", "make", "an", "exception", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "And yet you personally, if you had the chance, would send them all in jail?", "question_tokens": ["And", "yet", "you", "personally", ",", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", ",", "would", "send", "them", "all", "in", "jail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes, if I were king, I -- I would not allow people to go about burning the American flag.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "if", "I", "were", "king", ",", "I", "--", "I", "would", "not", "allow", "people", "to", "go", "about", "burning", "the", "American", "flag", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "-- an -- an opinion, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "an", "--", "an", "opinion", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, don't forget this person has to be convicted by a jury of 12 people who unanimously have to find that he was inciting to riot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "forget", "this", "person", "has", "to", "be", "convicted", "by", "a", "jury", "of", "12", "people", "who", "unanimously", "have", "to", "find", "that", "he", "was", "inciting", "to", "riot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, it really means a narrow reading, a crabbed reading of statutory words or of constitutional words.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "really", "means", "a", "narrow", "reading", ",", "a", "crabbed", "reading", "of", "statutory", "words", "or", "of", "constitutional", "words", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "And I -- I do think it's been abused, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "--", "I", "do", "think", "it", "'s", "been", "abused", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Can't you?", "question_tokens": ["Ca", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "It's -- it's -- it's utterly impossible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "utterly", "impossible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Would they not say this is abridging my speech?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "they", "not", "say", "this", "is", "abridging", "my", "speech", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Yes, but newspaper publishers aren't buying elections.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "newspaper", "publishers", "are", "n't", "buying", "elections", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "And it shouldn't be susceptible to the highest bidder, should it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "should", "n't", "be", "susceptible", "to", "the", "highest", "bidder", ",", "should", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Newspapers endorse political candidates all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["Newspapers", "endorse", "political", "candidates", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And are you going to limit the amount of money they can spend on it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "are", "you", "going", "to", "limit", "the", "amount", "of", "money", "they", "can", "spend", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Do you think the...", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Do you think, perhaps, they should be?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", ",", "perhaps", ",", "they", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Oh, I certainly think not.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "certainly", "think", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Is there any limit, in your eyes, to freedom of speech?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "limit", ",", "in", "your", "eyes", ",", "to", "freedom", "of", "speech", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Oh, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is -- is there -- what are the limitations in -- to you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "--", "is", "there", "--", "what", "are", "the", "limitations", "in", "--", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ":", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "I'm a textualist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "textualist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Isn't that a form of insurrection?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "a", "form", "of", "insurrection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Craig"], "LOCATION": ["Maryland"]}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ":", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "One of the more complex things about you, just -- which I -- I think is -- has been admired and criticized in equal measure, the case I would put to you, where I think it's interesting where you dissented against something where I think common sense would have dictated the opposite, was \"Maryland v. Craig,\" a young girl who had been abused by a child molester.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "more", "complex", "things", "about", "you", ",", "just", "--", "which", "I", "--", "I", "think", "is", "--", "has", "been", "admired", "and", "criticized", "in", "equal", "measure", ",", "the", "case", "I", "would", "put", "to", "you", ",", "where", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "interesting", "where", "you", "dissented", "against", "something", "where", "I", "think", "common", "sense", "would", "have", "dictated", "the", "opposite", ",", "was", "``", "Maryland", "v.", "Craig", ",", "''", "a", "young", "girl", "who", "had", "been", "abused", "by", "a", "child", "molester", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "-- abused and is actually traumatized by what happened?", "question_tokens": ["--", "abused", "and", "is", "actually", "traumatized", "by", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "CALIA: What it says it what it says.", "answer_tokens": ["CALIA", ":", "What", "it", "says", "it", "what", "it", "says", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Do you go home at night, when you dissent in that particular case, do you have misgivings about it, person -- on a personal level, or are you always able to divorce that from your, as you would say, legal responsibility to uphold the letter of the Constitution?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "go", "home", "at", "night", ",", "when", "you", "dissent", "in", "that", "particular", "case", ",", "do", "you", "have", "misgivings", "about", "it", ",", "person", "--", "on", "a", "personal", "level", ",", "or", "are", "you", "always", "able", "to", "divorce", "that", "from", "your", ",", "as", "you", "would", "say", ",", "legal", "responsibility", "to", "uphold", "the", "letter", "of", "the", "Constitution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "No, I -- I sleep very well at night knowing that I'm doing what I suppose -- what I am supposed to do, which is to apply -- to apply the Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "--", "I", "sleep", "very", "well", "at", "night", "knowing", "that", "I", "'m", "doing", "what", "I", "suppose", "--", "what", "I", "am", "supposed", "to", "do", ",", "which", "is", "to", "apply", "--", "to", "apply", "the", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Why were you so violently opposed to it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "so", "violently", "opposed", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I -- I wouldn't say violently.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "violently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Did they?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Of -- of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "--", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "It wouldn't have even entered their minds, would it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "n't", "have", "even", "entered", "their", "minds", ",", "would", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "What -- I -- I don't know why.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "--", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Why wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Because at the time, it was...", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "at", "the", "time", ",", "it", "was", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "They -- they didn't have wives and daughters that they cared about?", "question_tokens": ["They", "--", "they", "did", "n't", "have", "wives", "and", "daughters", "that", "they", "cared", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "They did, but it was not an issue that they would ever consider framing in the Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "did", ",", "but", "it", "was", "not", "an", "issue", "that", "they", "would", "ever", "consider", "framing", "in", "the", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "I mean, why would you be instinctively against that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "why", "would", "you", "be", "instinctively", "against", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "My view is regardless of whether you think prohibiting abortion is good or whether you think prohibiting abortion is bad, regardless of how you come out on that, my only point is the Constitution does not say anything about it.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "view", "is", "regardless", "of", "whether", "you", "think", "prohibiting", "abortion", "is", "good", "or", "whether", "you", "think", "prohibiting", "abortion", "is", "bad", ",", "regardless", "of", "how", "you", "come", "out", "on", "that", ",", "my", "only", "point", "is", "the", "Constitution", "does", "not", "say", "anything", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "My hardest?", "question_tokens": ["My", "hardest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "You want me to describe it really?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "me", "to", "describe", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Justice Scalia?", "question_tokens": ["Justice", "Scalia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Look it, I -- my court didn't -- didn't bring the case into the court.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "it", ",", "I", "--", "my", "court", "did", "n't", "--", "did", "n't", "bring", "the", "case", "into", "the", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "No regrets?", "question_tokens": ["No", "regrets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Oh, no regrets at all, especially since it's clear that the thing would have ended up the same way anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "regrets", "at", "all", ",", "especially", "since", "it", "'s", "clear", "that", "the", "thing", "would", "have", "ended", "up", "the", "same", "way", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "I mean, is it just me that thinks it's a bit weird that a guy can join the Supreme Court and literally not ask any questions?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "just", "me", "that", "thinks", "it", "'s", "a", "bit", "weird", "that", "a", "guy", "can", "join", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "and", "literally", "not", "ask", "any", "questions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Oh, that's not so unusual.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "so", "unusual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Are there clashes there?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "clashes", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "There -- there are clashes on -- on legal questions, but not personally.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "--", "there", "are", "clashes", "on", "--", "on", "legal", "questions", ",", "but", "not", "personally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Who told you that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "told", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I think I read it in some of the papers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "read", "it", "in", "some", "of", "the", "papers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Roberts"]}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "So you've had no falling out with Justice Roberts?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "had", "no", "falling", "out", "with", "Justice", "Roberts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I'm not going to talk about -- no, I haven't had a falling out with Justice Roberts.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "talk", "about", "--", "no", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "had", "a", "falling", "out", "with", "Justice", "Roberts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Roberts"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Loud words exchanged?", "question_tokens": ["Loud", "words", "exchanged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Slamming of doors?", "question_tokens": ["Slamming", "of", "doors", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Nothing like that?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Nothing like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ruth Bader Ginsburg"]}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Best buddies?", "question_tokens": ["Best", "buddies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "My best buddy on the court is Ruth Bader Ginsburg, has always been.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "best", "buddy", "on", "the", "court", "is", "Ruth", "Bader", "Ginsburg", ",", "has", "always", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "What do you like to do when you're not presiding in the Supreme Court?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "like", "to", "do", "when", "you", "'re", "not", "presiding", "in", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I like to play tennis.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "to", "play", "tennis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "You've been hunting with Dick Cheney, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "hunting", "with", "Dick", "Cheney", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I have, indeed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", ",", "indeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "How -- how carefully do you think, before you accept an invitation to go hunting with Dick Cheney, how hard do you think about that as a potential conflict?", "question_tokens": ["How", "--", "how", "carefully", "do", "you", "think", ",", "before", "you", "accept", "an", "invitation", "to", "go", "hunting", "with", "Dick", "Cheney", ",", "how", "hard", "do", "you", "think", "about", "that", "as", "a", "potential", "conflict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, in that case, I had accepted the invitation long before the case that was the alleged source of the conflict was before the court.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "that", "case", ",", "I", "had", "accepted", "the", "invitation", "long", "before", "the", "case", "that", "was", "the", "alleged", "source", "of", "the", "conflict", "was", "before", "the", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Does that annoy you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "annoy", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "No, I -- I usually don't read it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "--", "I", "usually", "do", "n't", "read", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNPS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "A good judge will decide cases based on a governing text that go against what the judge might think is wise policy, isn't that true?", "question_tokens": ["A", "good", "judge", "will", "decide", "cases", "based", "on", "a", "governing", "text", "that", "go", "against", "what", "the", "judge", "might", "think", "is", "wise", "policy", ",", "is", "n't", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Look it, I have ruled against the government when Republicans were in the administration and I've ruled for the government when Democrats were in the admin -- I couldn't care less who the president is or what the administration is.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "it", ",", "I", "have", "ruled", "against", "the", "government", "when", "Republicans", "were", "in", "the", "administration", "and", "I", "'ve", "ruled", "for", "the", "government", "when", "Democrats", "were", "in", "the", "admin", "--", "I", "could", "n't", "care", "less", "who", "the", "president", "is", "or", "what", "the", "administration", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "-- from a politically motivated manner?", "question_tokens": ["--", "from", "a", "politically", "motivated", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Not a single one of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "a", "single", "one", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Souter", "John Paul Stevens"]}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "WRB", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "-- does it offend you that his integrity would be questioned like that?", "question_tokens": ["--", "does", "it", "offend", "you", "that", "his", "integrity", "would", "be", "questioned", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "It -- it offends me that -- that -- that people point to the fact -- and they didn't used to be able to when -- when -- when David Souter and John Paul Stevens were still on the court.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "--", "it", "offends", "me", "that", "--", "that", "--", "that", "people", "point", "to", "the", "fact", "--", "and", "they", "did", "n't", "used", "to", "be", "able", "to", "when", "--", "when", "--", "when", "David", "Souter", "and", "John", "Paul", "Stevens", "were", "still", "on", "the", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "And you're married a very long time to a long-suffering woman, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "married", "a", "very", "long", "time", "to", "a", "long-suffering", "woman", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I'd say so, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "so", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Have I ever broken the law?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "ever", "broken", "the", "law", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Have you ever been caught?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "been", "caught", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "-- in your life?", "question_tokens": ["--", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "-- I am pretty much a law-abiding sort.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "am", "pretty", "much", "a", "law-abiding", "sort", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "My guilty pleasure?", "question_tokens": ["My", "guilty", "pleasure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "How can -- how can it be pleasurable if it's guilty?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "--", "how", "can", "it", "be", "pleasurable", "if", "it", "'s", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I've got lots of guilty pleasures.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "lots", "of", "guilty", "pleasures", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Now, you've been married for how long?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "married", "for", "how", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Fifty-two years.", "answer_tokens": ["Fifty-two", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "How many grandchildren are there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "grandchildren", "are", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Thirty-three.", "answer_tokens": ["Thirty-three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What has been the secret of -- of such a longstanding marriage, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "the", "secret", "of", "--", "of", "such", "a", "longstanding", "marriage", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Maureen made it very clear early on that if we split up, I would get the children.", "answer_tokens": ["Maureen", "made", "it", "very", "clear", "early", "on", "that", "if", "we", "split", "up", ",", "I", "would", "get", "the", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Did you mean that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "mean", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "She has -- she has worked very hard.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "has", "--", "she", "has", "worked", "very", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Prop -- properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["Prop", "--", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Hmmm.", "answer_tokens": ["Hmmm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Will you ever retire?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "ever", "retire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Of course I'll retire.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "'ll", "retire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 567, "question": "And as -- as we sit here now, what would you say your greatest achievement has been as a Supreme Court justice?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "--", "as", "we", "sit", "here", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "your", "greatest", "achievement", "has", "been", "as", "a", "Supreme", "Court", "justice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Wow!", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "The framing of the Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "framing", "of", "the", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madison"]}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What's the difference, really?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "No I -- I don't -- I don't use the -- Madison's notes as authoritative on the meaning of the Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "use", "the", "--", "Madison", "'s", "notes", "as", "authoritative", "on", "the", "meaning", "of", "the", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Why are you so convinced that these guys, over 200 years ago, were so right?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "so", "convinced", "that", "these", "guys", ",", "over", "200", "years", "ago", ",", "were", "so", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "You have to read the Federalist Papers to answer that question.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "read", "the", "Federalist", "Papers", "to", "answer", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you wish we had a few of them now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "we", "had", "a", "few", "of", "them", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I wish we had a few of them now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wish", "we", "had", "a", "few", "of", "them", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Do you still get a little thrill when you come in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "get", "a", "little", "thrill", "when", "you", "come", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Most in history?", "question_tokens": ["Most", "in", "history", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "No, no, no --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "In my lifetime?", "question_tokens": ["In", "my", "lifetime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "In your lifetime, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "your", "lifetime", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "What made him special?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "him", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "He had a way of -- he was the great communicator.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "a", "way", "of", "--", "he", "was", "the", "great", "communicator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Did he give you any advice when he put you forward?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "give", "you", "any", "advice", "when", "he", "put", "you", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Did he say anything?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "say", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "Would you tell me if he had?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "tell", "me", "if", "he", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "He almost got my name right.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "almost", "got", "my", "name", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Do you ever have to pay for spaghetti bolognese in New York?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "have", "to", "pay", "for", "spaghetti", "bolognese", "in", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I have a lot of Italian friends.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "Italian", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120718pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "What do you call it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Pasta con sarde (ph) I think is the name of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Pasta", "con", "sarde", "(", "ph", ")", "I", "think", "is", "the", "name", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]